<strings>
	<!-- Register System as App section -->
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_register_system_header"><![CDATA[Register System as Twitter Client]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_register_system_note"><![CDATA[<p>Before you can use this trigger action, you need to register your system as a Twitter client. This trigger action uses OAuth to authenticate with Twitter, and
		therefore requires you to obtain API access first. You only need to do this once for all Update Twitter Status trigger actions within the system.</p>

		<p>To register your system, go to Twitter's <a href="http://twitter.com/oauth_clients"  tagret="_blank" >OAuth Clients</a> page, and click on &quot;Create a new application&quot;.
		Enter any system root URL as the Callback URL (it will be ignored - Matrix will provide it with a correct callback URL).</p>

		<p>When you complete the registration, it will provide you with a <strong>consumer key</strong> and a
		<strong>consumer secret</strong> string, which you need to enter below. </p>
		
		<p>Apps are created Read Only by default. Make sure Read and Write is selected in the setting tab after registration.</p>]]>
	</string>


	<!-- Client Credentials section -->
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_client_credentials_header"><![CDATA[Client Credentials]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_client_credentials_note"><![CDATA[<p>Once you have entered the <strong>consumer key</strong> and <strong>consumer secret</strong> string into the boxes above and commit, a &quot;Sign in with Twitter&quot; link will appear. Click this and follow the prompts to complete the authentication process. Remember to sign in with the Twitter account you want to tweet to.</p>

		<p><strong class="sq-backend-warning">You will temporarily leave the Matrix backend during this process</strong> - permission is granted through the Twitter site. Your Matrix session will remain active (subject to session length rules), and you will be redirected back to this trigger once authentication is complete.</p>]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_client_credentials_key"><![CDATA[Consumer key:]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_client_credentials_secret"><![CDATA[Consumer secret string:]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_client_credentials_status"><![CDATA[Authentication status:]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_client_credentials_status_no_consumer"><![CDATA[<strong style="color: #f00">Error: no client credentials provided.</strong><br/>Please enter the Consumer Key and Consumer Secret provided by Twitter to attempt authentication.]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_client_credentials_status_no_unlocked"><![CDATA[<strong>Not started</strong><br/>lock this trigger to begin the authentication process.]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_client_credentials_status_no"><![CDATA[<strong>Not started</strong><br/><strong><a href="%s" tagret="_blank" >Sign in with Twitter</a></strong> to connect to an account]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_client_credentials_status_yes"><![CDATA[<strong style="color: #060">Connected</strong> to <strong>%s</strong>]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_client_credentials_status_request_error"><![CDATA[Authentication status:]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_client_credentials_deauthorise"><![CDATA[Use another account]]></string>


	<!-- Tweet Format section -->
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_tweet_format_header"><![CDATA[Tweet Format]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_tweet_format_note"><![CDATA[<p>You can use any global keyword, or asset keyword (which uses the triggering asset). In addition, you can use the keyword
		<strong>&#37;asset_short_url&#37;</strong> to refer to the shortest URL that can be used to point to this asset - whether this is the main URL or a remap. It may be useful
		to add an <strong>Add Remap</strong> action before this one, to ensure a short URL (based on asset ID) is created which can then be used by this action.</p>

		<p>Due to the variable length of keyword replacements, the box above will <strong>not</strong> limit you to 140 characters. You may determine what occurs when the
		length of the tweet (with all keywords replaced) is longer than 140 characters. If you choose <strong>Abbreviate where possible</strong>, the parts of text which
		are not links will be abbreviated to reduce the size to 140 characters, where possible - if not reasonably possible, the trigger will fail. Or you can choose to
		simply <strong>Fail the trigger</strong>.</p>]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_tweet_format_format"><![CDATA[Format of tweets:]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_tweet_format_iftoolong"><![CDATA[If tweet too long:]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_tweet_format_iftoolong_option_abbrev"><![CDATA[Abbreviate tweet if possible]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_tweet_format_iftoolong_option_fail"><![CDATA[Fail the trigger]]></string>
	<string source="trigger_action_update_twitter_status_tweet_format_char_count"><![CDATA[(Characters left: <span id="%1$s_tweet_length">%2$s</span>)]]></string>

</strings>
